Guide to the Judson Memorial Church Archive MSS.094
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series C: General Archives
  - Subseries 8: Minister-Generated Materials
    - Moody Sermons-How Can I Get Ready? 12/13/1981 (Box 50, Folder 59)
    - Moody Sermons-The Profundity of Subway Scrawling, 1/3/1982 (Box 50, Folder 60)
    - Moody Sermons-Human Vengeance and Divine Mercy, 1/31/1982 (Box 50, Folder 61)
    - Moody Sermons-The Missing Dimension in Our Life, 2/21/1982 (Box 50, Folder 62)
    - Moody Sermons-Words About Easter, 4/11/1982 (Box 50, Folder 63)
    - Moody Sermons-Idolatry of Religion, 4/25/1982 (Box 50, Folder 64)
    - Moody Sermons-Meditation for Peace Sabbath, 2/23/1982 (Box 50, Folder 65)
    - Moody Sermons-What Is Truth in a World of Lies? 9/12/1982 (Box 50, Folder 66)
    - Moody Sermons-Old and New Rituals, 9/26/1982 (Box 50, Folder 67)
    - Moody Sermons-World Without Guilt, 10/10/1982 (Box 50, Folder 68)
    - Moody Sermons-Agape Meal Meditation, 12/5/1982 (Box 50, Folder 69)
    - Moody Sermons-Who Tempted the Serpent, 2/27/1983 (Box 50, Folder 70)
    - Moody Sermons-Dangers of a Therapeutic State, 5/15/1983 (Box 50, Folder 71)
    - Moody Sermons-Apocalypse and Us, 6/12/1983 (Box 50, Folder 72)
    - Moody Sermons-El Salvador and Nicaragua: Will We Learn from Our Past? 10/9/1983 (Box 50, Folder 73)
    - Moody Sermons-Reflections on a Journey: Report on Nicaragua Trip, 2/5/1984 (Box 50, Folder 74)
    - Moody Sermons-Humans Are Congenital Believers, 9/30/1984 (Box 50, Folder 75)
    - Moody Sermons-Apocalyptic Prophecy and Prophetic Vision, 11/25/1984 (Box 50, Folder 76)
    - Moody Sermons-Architectural Symbols and Spiritual Truths, Judson Weekend/1984 (Box 50, Folder 77)
    - Moody Sermons-Ordination Sermon for Dan Shenk, 1/20/1985 (Box 50, Folder 78)
    - Moody Sermons-In Memoriam, 4/21/1985 (Box 50, Folder 79)
    - Moody Sermons-Rambo, Regan, and Reality, 7/14/1985 (Box 50, Folder 80)
    - Moody Sermons-Beliefs That Are Bothersome, 10/11/1985 (Box 50, Folder 81)
    - Moody Sermons-Beliefs That Are Bothersome, 11/10/1985 (Box 50, Folder 82)
    - Moody Sermons-Suffering That Produces Hope, 2/23/1986 (Box 50, Folder 83)
    - Moody Sermons-The Conspiracy of Silence on Suicide, 3/9/1986 (Box 50, Folder 84)
    - Moody Sermons-Reflections on Coming of Age, 4/13/1986 (Box 50, Folder 85)
    - Moody Sermons-The New Fundamentalists, 5/11/1986 (Box 50, Folder 86)
    - Moody Sermons-My Body and Our Body, 6/1/1986 (Box 50, Folder 87)
    - Moody Sermons-Meditations on Homosexuality, 6/29/1986 (Box 50, Folder 88)
    - Moody Sermons-Confessions of an Embarrassed Baptist, 10/26/1986 (Box 50, Folder 89)
    - Moody Sermons-The Elusiveness of the Spiritual, 1/11/1987 (Box 50, Folder 90)
    - Moody Sermons-Encounters of an Ultimate Kind, 3/22/1987 (Box 50, Folder 91)
    - Moody Sermons-Is the American Dream Dead? 5/31/1987 (Box 50, Folder 92)
    - Moody Sermons-Confessions of a Sensuous Self, 7/12/1987 (Box 50, Folder 93)
    - Moody Sermons-Moody Looking Inward, 9/20/1987 (Box 50, Folder 94)
    - Moody Sermons-Alternatives to Marriage, 11/8/1987 (Box 50, Folder 95)
    - Moody Sermons-Wanted: More Skeptics, 1/10/1988 (Box 50, Folder 96)
    - Moody Sermons-The Church's Betrayal of Women, 1/24/1988 (Box 50, Folder 97)
    - Moody Sermons-The Cruciform Shape of Things, 3/20/1988 (Box 50, Folder 98)
    - Moody Sermons-Mideast Crisis: Beyond Present Polarities, 4/24/1988 (Box 50, Folder 99)
    - Moody Sermons-The Past: Love It and Leave It, 8/21/1988 (Box 50, Folder 100)
    - Moody Sermons-Meditation, 9/25/1988 (Box 50, Folder 101)
    - Moody Sermons-Reflection of Faith on Health and Illness, 11/13/1988 (Box 50, Folder 102)
    - Moody Sermons-Meditation on King, 1/15/1989 (Box 50, Folder 103)
    - Moody Sermons-Meditation on Easter, 3/26/1989 (Box 50, Folder 104)
    - Moody Sermons-There Is More to Aging Than Death, 4/16/1989 (Box 50, Folder 105)
    - Moody Sermons-What Is New About New Age Religions? 5/21/1989 (Box 50, Folder 106)
    - Moody Sermons-Our Lives Are One Big Triage, 6/4/1989 (Box 50, Folder 107)
    - Moody Sermons-Nostalgia as a Form of Escapism, 9/17/1989 (Box 50, Folder 108)
    - Moody Sermons-The Temptation of a Godless World, 11/26/1989 (Box 50, Folder 109)
    - Moody Sermons-Centennial Events/Moody's Introduction, 1/1990 (Box 50, Folder 110)
    - Moody Sermons-Looking Back, Looking Forward: The Judson Centennial, 1/7/1990 (Box 50, Folder 111)
    - Moody Sermons-Money as Meaning and Metaphor, 3/4/1990 (Box 50, Folder 112)
    - Moody Sermons-History as Antidote to Drug Hysteria, 3/18/1990 (Box 50, Folder 113)
    - Moody Sermons-Pardon, Is My Eschatology Showing? 5/20/1990 (Box 50, Folder 114)
    - Moody Sermons-The Burden of Forgiveness, 7/22/1990 (Box 50, Folder 115)
    - Moody Sermons-Today's Most Feared Four-Letter Word, 9/16/1990 (Box 50, Folder 116)
    - Moody Sermons-Homecoming Meditation, 10/7/1990 (Box 50, Folder 117)
    - Moody Sermons-Graven Images, Religious Blasphemy and Dirty Pictures,11/11/1990 (Box 50, Folder 118)
    - Moody Sermons-The Mirage of Victory and Peace in Desert Storm, 4/7/1991 (Box 50, Folder 119)
    - Moody Sermons-The Church Wrestles with Change, 5/5/1991 (Box 50, Folder 120)
    - Moody Sermons-The Changing Tides of Love, 5/12/1991 (Box 50, Folder 121)
    - Moody Sermons-How Far Have We Come? 6/30/1991 (Box 50, Folder 122)
    - Moody Sermons-Say the Right Thing or Else, 9/15/1991 (Box 50, Folder 123)
    - Moody Sermons-The Church as Counterculture, 9/22/1991 (Box 50, Folder 124)
    - Moody Sermons-The New Masculinity or the Old Machismo? 9/29/1991 (Box 50, Folder 125)
    - Moody Sermons-Does a Religion of Revelation Breed Exclusivity?10/20/1991 (Box 50, Folder 126)
    - Moody Sermons-Prisons and Ghettos: The Nurturing of Hopelessness,10/27/1991 (Box 50, Folder 127)
    - Moody Sermons-Jesus Incognito, 12/8/1991 (Box 50, Folder 128)
    - Moody Sermons-Christmas, Creatures and the Creche, 12/15/1991 (Box 50, Folder 129)
    - Moody Sermons-Two Meditations on the Passing of Time, 12/29/1991 (Box 50, Folder 130)
    - Moody Sermons-Does Politics Really Matter? 3/15/1992 (Box 50, Folder 131)
    - Moody Sermons-The Betrayal of our Children's Needs, 3/22/1992 (Box 50, Folder 132)
    - Moody Sermons-Some Parting Words, 4/26/1992 (Box 50, Folder 133)
    - Moody-Speeches, Conference Papers, Sermons, etc., undated (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Moody-Other Remarks, 1985-86, 1985-1986 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Moody-Other Remarks, 1988-89, 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Moody-Other Remarks, 1990-92, 1990-1992 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Petty-Judson Memorial Papers, undated (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Petty-Undated Papers (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Petty-Staff in the Petty Era, undated (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Petty-Pamphlets, undated (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Petty-Letter of Transfer to Judson Memorial Church, 3/3/1916 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Petty-Petty Starts Sunday Discussion/Newspaper Clippings, 1918 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Petty-Prohibition Papers, 1918 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Petty- Luncheon Invitation, 1921 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Pickle-Internship Year, 9/1959-9/1960, 1959-1960 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Pickle-Sermon: The Intimacy of Eternity, 8/31/1961 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Scott-Writings, Notes, Sermons, etc. 1955-60, 1955-1960 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Scott-Sermon: The Difficulty with Thanksgiving, 11/23/1958 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Scott-Photograph of Scott, 1959 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Spike-His Call to Judson/Dedication Sermon, 1949 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Spike-Report on Greenwich Village and Programs [ 1949?] (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Spike-Fellowship Programs, 1950's (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Spike-Sermons, 1951-55, 1951-1955 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Spike-Community Service Program, undated (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Spike-Miscellaneous Papers, Notes, and Letters, undated (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Spike-Converse, Paul-License to Preach, 7/29/1951 (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - Spike-Memo regarding Program to Cliff McDonald, 10/27/1952 (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - Spike-60th Anniversary of Judson, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - Spike-Articles about Judson Memorial Church, 1953-58, 1953-1958 (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - Spike-"Historic Judson Church in Greenwich Village" The City Church, 9/10/1954 (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - Spike-Letter of Resignation, 10/9/1955 (Box 51, Folder 29)
    - Spike-Valedictory, 12/1955 (Box 51, Folder 30)
    - Spike-Address/Conference on Urban Communication, 10/22/1958 (Box 51, Folder 31)
    - Spike-Reminiscences about Judson Memorial Church from 1949-56 [presented at the congregational meeting on 11/1964], 1949-1956 [presented at the congregational meeting on 11/1964] (Box 51, Folder 32)
    - Spike-Photographs of Spike, undated (Box 51, Folder 33)
    - Suarez-Manuscripts and Notes, [1988-?] (Box 51, Folder 34)
    - Suarez-Sermons, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 35)
    - Suarez-Sermons, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 36)
    - Suarez-Sermons, 1989 (Box 51, Folder 37)
    - Thomsen-Assistant to Petty, Fall 1923-12/1924, 1923-19241924 (Box 51, Folder 38)
    - Tingley-Proposed Program and Organization, 1946 (Box 51, Folder 39)
    - Tingley-Resignation Letter, 4/24/1948 (Box 51, Folder 40)
    - Visiting Pastors-Sermons, 1960-74, 1960-1974 (Box 51, Folder 41)
  - Subseries 9: Correspondence
    - Carmen-Photographs of Arlene Carmen (Box 51, Folder 42)
    - Carmen-General, 1982-83, 1982-1983 (Box 51, Folder 43)
    - Carmen-General, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 44)
    - Carmen-General, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 45)
    - Carmen-General, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 46)
    - Carmen-General, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 47)
    - Carmen-General, 1987 [cont.] (Box 51, Folder 48)
    - Carmen-General, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Carmen-General, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Carmen-General, 1990-93, 1990-1993 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Carmen-General [no date], undated (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Carmines-General, 1963-68, 1963-1968 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Carmines-General, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Carmines-Travel, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Carmines-General, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Carmines-Travel, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Carmines-General, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Carmines-Travel, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Carmines-General, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Carmines-General, 1972 [cont.] (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Carmines-Travel, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Carmines-"Joan" Record, 1972-77, 1972-1977 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Carmines-General, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Carmines-General, 1973 [cont.] (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Carmines-Regarding Scripts, 1973-75, 1973-1975 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Carmines-Permissions/Requests, 1973-78, 1973-1978 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Carmines-General, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Carmines-General, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Carmines-General, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Carmines-General, 1976 [cont.] (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Carmines-General, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Carmines-General, 1977 [cont.] (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Carmines-Travel, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Carmines-General, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Carmines-Travel, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Carmines-Recommendations, 1978-80, 1978-1980 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Carmines-General, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Carmines-Travel, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Carmines-General, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Carmines-Travel, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Carmines-General, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Hancock-Cosmopolitan Magazine Faith Healing, 1984 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Hancock-Cosmopolitan Magazine Faith Healing, 1984 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Hancock-Cosmopolitan Magazine Faith Healing, 1984-1985 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Hancock-General, 1982-1983 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Hancock-General, 1984 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Hancock-General, 1985 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Hancock-General, undated (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Hosie-General/Note Regarding Materials on Sharecropper Movie, 1932 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Hosie-Resignation, 1937 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Hosie-General [Carmen/Moody]1976-94, 1976-1994 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Judson-Letter of Response to Call from Berean Baptist Church,1881 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Judson-General, 1886-90, 1886-1990 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Judson-General/Picture Tracts, 1897 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Judson-General/Picture Tracts, 1898 (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Judson-General Responses, 1901-11, 1901-1911 (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - Judson-Requests for Aid, Work, References, 1901 (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - Judson-Requests for Aid, Work, References, 1902 (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - Judson-Requests for Aid, Work, References, 1902-04, 1902-1904 (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - Judson-General, 1902-12, 1902-1912 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Judson-General/Financial Statements, 1903 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Judson-General, 1903 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Judson-General, 1904 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Judson-General, 1905 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Judson-General, 1906 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Judson-General, 1907 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Judson-General, 1908 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Judson-General, 1909 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Judson-General, 1910 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Judson-General, 1911 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Judson-General, 1912-13, 1912-1913 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Moody-Robin Hood vs. McCarthyism, 1954 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Moody-General, 1956-60, 1956-1960 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Moody-General, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Moody-General, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Moody-General, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Moody-General, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Moody-Matteson/Moody (regarding Moody's nomination to the M & M Board)1964 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Moody-John Lawrence, 1964-66, 1964-1966 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Moody-General, 1965 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Moody-Robert F. Kennedy (regarding the issue of narcotics addiction) 7/6/1965 (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Moody-History, 1965-71, 1965-1971 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Moody-Grace Goodman, 8/22/1966 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Moody-General, 1967-68, 1967-1968 (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Moody-Travel, 1967-68, 1967-1968 (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - Moody-IDO-C, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Moody-General, 1969-71, 1969-1971 (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - Moody-Foundations, 1969-71, 1969-1971 (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - Moody-Regarding Women's Liberation, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 30)
    - Moody-General, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 31)
    - Moody-General, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 32)
    - Moody-Personal, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 33)
    - Moody-General, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 34)
    - Moody-Personal, 1974-75, 1974-1975 (Box 54, Folder 35)
    - Moody-General, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 36)
    - Moody-General, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 37)
    - Moody-Personal, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 38)
    - Moody-General, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 39)
    - Moody-Personal, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 40)
    - Moody-General, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 41)
    - Moody-General, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 42)
    - Moody-Regarding March on St. Patrick's Cathedral in Support of Abortion Rights, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 43)
    - Moody-General, 1981-83, 1981-1983 (Box 54, Folder 44)
    - Moody-General, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 45)
    - Moody-Regarding Linnette Jenkins, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 46)
    - Moody-General, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Moody-General, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Moody-General, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Moody-General, 1988 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Moody-General, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Moody-Letter to Congregation regarding the resignation of Suarez, 4/14/1989 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Moody-Centennial, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Moody-Letter to Congregation regarding Bean and Zeh on Staff, 5/9/1989 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Moody-Justice Blackmun Letter Regarding Bulletin Board, 9/12/1989 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Moody-Steve Joseph (regarding needle exchange) 9/26/1989 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Moody-General, 1990-92, 1990-1992 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Petty-General, 1914-16, 1914-1916 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Petty-Financial Correspondence, 1917- 19, 1917-1919 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Petty-General, 1917- 18, 1917-1918 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Petty-General, 1917- 18 [cont.], 1917-1918 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Petty-General, 19 18 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Petty-General, 19 18 [cont.] (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Petty-General, 1918-20, 1918-1920 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Petty-General, 1918-20 [cont.], 1918-1920 (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Petty-General, 19 18-20 [cont.], 1918-1920 (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Petty-General, 19 18-20 [cont.], 1918-1920 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Petty-General, 19 18-20 [cont.], 1918-1920 (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - Petty-General, 1920 (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - Petty-General, 1920 [cont.] (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - Petty-General, 1921-22, 1921-1922 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Petty-General, 1922 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Petty-General, 1922 [cont.] (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Petty-General, 1922 [cont.] (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Petty-General, 1922 [cont.] (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Petty-General, 1925-26, 1925-1926 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Spike-General, 1950-53, 1950-1953 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Spike-General, 1954 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Spike-General, 1955-56, 1955-1956 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Spike-General, 1958-59, 1958-1959 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Tingley-General, 1946 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - General Church Correspondence-1941-46, 1941-1946 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - General Church Correspondence-1948-49, 1948-1949 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - General Church Correspondence-1950-53, 1950-1953 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - General Church Correspondence-NYU Heat Supply, 1951-53, 1951-1953 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - General Church Correspondence-1954-59, 1954-1959 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - General Church Correspondence-1960-64, 1960-1964 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - General Church Correspondence-1968-70, 1968-1970 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - General Church Correspondence-1970-71, 1970-1971 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - General Church Correspondence-1972 (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - General Church Correspondence-1973 (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - General Church Correspondence-1974 (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - General Church Correspondence-1975 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - General Church Correspondence-1976 (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - General Church Correspondence-1977 (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - General Church Correspondence-A Voice in the Village mail orders, 1977-84, 1977-1984 (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - General Church Correspondence-1978 (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - General Church Correspondence-1979 (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - General Church Correspondence-1981-84, 1981-1984 (Box 56, Folder 29)
    - General Church Correspondence-Treasurer's Letters to Pledgers, 1982-91, 1982-1991 (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - General Church Correspondence-Real Estate/Insurance, 1983-84, 1983-1984 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - General Church Correspondence-Copier, 1984-85, 1984-1985 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - General Church Correspondence-Property, Insurance, Personnel, 1984-86, 1984-1986 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - General Church Correspondence-1985 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - General Church Correspondence-1986 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - General Church Correspondence-1987 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - General Church Correspondence-1988 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - General Church Correspondence-Trincia/Grace House Rent Acknowledgement, 1988-89, 1988-1989 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - General Church Correspondence-1989 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - General Church Correspondence-1990-94, 1990-1994 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 10: Community/ Social Action
    - AIDS Task Force-AIDS Resource Center, 1984-85, 1984-1985 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - AIDS Task Force-PWA Egg Yolk Extract Distribution at Judson, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - AIDS Task Force-AIDS Movement and Meditation Group, 1988-89, 1988-1989 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - AIDS Task Force-HIV Project-Protocol, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - AIDS Task Force-HIV Project-Consent and Release, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - AIDS Task Force-HIV Project-Memo and Speculation, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - AIDS Task Force-HIV Project-McGrath Journal Article, 4/1989 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - AIDS Task Force-HIV Project-U. S. Patent, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - AIDS Task Force-HIV Project-Product Packaging, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - AIDS Task Force-HIV Project-Medical Releases, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - AIDS Task Force-HIV Project-Lab Work Information, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - AIDS Task Force-HIV Project-Press Clips, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - AIDS Task Force-HIV Project-Genelabs P. R. 1989 (Box 57, Folder 23)
    - AIDS Task Force-HIV Project-CDC Classification Systems, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 24)
    - AIDS Task Force-HIV Project-CARE Management, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 25)
    - AIDS Task Force-HIV Project-Appointments, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 26)
    - AIDS Task Force-HIV Project-Lab/Diagnostic, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 27)
    - AIDS Task Force-HIV Project-Adverse Experiences, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 28)
    - AIDS Task Force-HIV Project-References, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 29)
    - AIDS Task Force-HIV Project-Pre-Treatment, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 30)
    - AIDS Task Force-HIV Project-Day 1 & 2, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 31)
    - AIDS Task Force-HIV Project-Day 3, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 32)
    - AIDS Task Force-HIV Project-Day 7 & 8, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 33)
    - AIDS Task Force-HIV Project-Day 10, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 34)
    - AIDS Task Force-HIV Project-Day 14 & 15, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 35)
    - AIDS Task Force-HIV Project-Day 18, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 36)
    - AIDS Task Force-HIV Project-Day 21, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 37)
    - AIDS Task Force-HIV Project-Month 2-6, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 38)
    - AIDS Task Force-HIV Project-Study Termination, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 39)
    - AIDS Task Force-Compound Q, Summer/Fall 1989 (Box 57, Folder 40)
    - AIDS Task Force-Compound Q, The New York Times Correspondence, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 41)
    - AIDS Task Force-1991-93, 1991-1993 (Box 57, Folder 42)
    - AIDS Task Force-HIV Seroprevalence Semi-Annual Report, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 43)
    - AIDS Task Force-Arrest of Madya Rivera, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 44)
    - AIDS Task Force-Suicide and AIDS, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 45)
    - AIDS Task Force-AIDS Articles [see oversize], undated (Box 57, Folder 46)
    - AIDS Task Force-Surviving and Thriving with AIDS, vol. 2, undated (Box 57, Folder 47)
    - Anti-Poverty Program-Judson Application, 1966 (Box 57, Folder 48)
    - Anti-Poverty Program-Administration, undated (Box 57, Folder 49)
    - Anti-Poverty Program-Play Street, Summer 1966 (Box 57, Folder 50)
    - Cancer Consultation Service-Prospectus, 5/1/1980 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Cancer Consultation Service-Project and General Information, 1985-86, 1985-1986 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Cancer Consultation Service-Applications, 1985-86, 1985-1986 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Cancer Consultation Service-Funding Requests 1985-86, 1985-1986 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Cancer Consultation Service-Final Report, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Cancer Consultation Service-Cancer Help Project Support Group Roster, 1987 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Central American Ministries-Sanctuary Committee (El Salvador) 1984-85, 1984-1985 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Central American Ministries-Report on Trip to El Salvador, undated (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Central American Ministries-1985-86, 1985-1986 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Central American Ministries-Committee, 1985-86, 1985-1986 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Central American Ministries-Publications, 1985-88, 1985-1988 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Central American Ministries-March on Washington, 4/25/1987 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Central American Ministries-1988-89, 1988-1989 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Central Park Baptist Church-1950's & 1960's (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Central Park Baptist Church-1950's & 1960's [cont.] (Box 58, Folder 15)